let questions=[ //games
{ numb : 1,
question:"Unity is ....?",
answer:"Game engine",
options:[
"Game engine",
"Photo editer",
"Gimp",
"ProBuilder"
]
},
{ numb : 2,
question:"Scenes are included in .....floder.",
answer:"Build",
options:[
"Build",
"asset",
"library",
"project Setting"
]
},
{ numb : 3,
question:"The transform component determine the",
answer:"All of the above",
options:[
"position",
"rotation",
"scale",
"All of the above"
]
},
{ numb : 4,
question:"What is the most important component of unity?",
answer:"Transform",
options:[
"Toolbar",
"Scene View",
"Hicrarchy",
"Transform"
]
},
{ numb : 5,
question:"Inspector in unity is a .... panel.   ",
answer:"Context-sensitive",
options:[
"Context-sensitive",
"Content-sensitive",
"Context-complex",
"none"
]
},
{ numb : 6,
question:"Assetbundlers are ....in unity.",
answer:"Files",
options:[
"Content",
"Files",
"Objects",
"Tags"
]
},
{ numb : 7,
question:"Non-rigid object in Unity?",
answer:"Both",
options:[
"Deformable",
"Breakable",
"Both",
"None"
]
},
{ numb :8 ,
question:"Prefab in unity is referred for .... template.",
answer:"Pre-fabricated object",
options:[
"Pre-fabricated object",
"fabricated object",
"Post-fabricated object",
"None"
]
},
{ numb : 9,
question:"To make copy of an object you can use ....function",
answer:"Instantiate()",
options:[
"Instantiate()",
"Func()",
"Spawn()",
"object"
]
},
{ numb :10 ,
question:"Use of Asset Bundles in Unity?",
answer:"Uploading",
options:[
"Uploading",
"Downloading",
"Editing",
"Deleting"
]
},
];